[{"answer": "I'm looking over, I see people going -- don't do it, don't do it.", "docId": "111009pmt", "aSentId": 3, "question": "If you could choose one partner, who would it be?", "qSentId": 2}, {"answer": "Yes.", "docId": "111009pmt", "aSentId": 22, "question": "You're Irish descent, but you're Scottish basically, aren't you?", "qSentId": 21}, {"answer": "Yes.", "docId": "111009pmt", "aSentId": 41, "question": "Six hours a day?", "qSentId": 40}, {"answer": "Really, really did.", "docId": "111009pmt", "aSentId": 48, "question": "Did it really?", "qSentId": 47}, {"answer": "No, because I look ridiculous.", "docId": "111009pmt", "aSentId": 63, "question": "Was it a kind of sense of absolute euphoria?", "qSentId": 62}, {"answer": "This is a great start to an interview, here you are fat, and now let's talk about the time you were fired.", "docId": "111009pmt", "aSentId": 75, "question": "You went to Edinburgh Festival, the famous arts and creative festival in Scotland and basically got wrecked, right?", "qSentId": 74}, {"answer": "I was shackled, yes.", "docId": "111009pmt", "aSentId": 116, "question": "You were actually shackled, right?", "qSentId": 115}, {"answer": "That was a wake up moment, yes, but in truth I had a few of them.", "docId": "111009pmt", "aSentId": 120, "question": "Was that a wake-up moment?", "qSentId": 119}, {"answer": "Yes, I don't think I would have, I don't think I'd be alive today to be honest, and I don't say that lightly.", "docId": "111009pmt", "aSentId": 132, "question": "Do you ever wonder what may have happened if you passed your law degree, if you passed exams, if you'd become a lawyer?", "qSentId": 131}, {"answer": "Yes, she did.", "docId": "111009pmt", "aSentId": 141, "question": "Did she realize as what you were supposed to be doing?", "qSentId": 140}, {"answer": "Let's go, get up.", "docId": "111009pmt", "aSentId": 166, "question": "What are you doing?", "qSentId": 165}, {"answer": "It's the way you introduced the movie is the very same reason I wanted to do it.", "docId": "111009pmt", "aSentId": 185, "question": "Why this?", "qSentId": 184}, {"answer": "Yes.", "docId": "111009pmt", "aSentId": 196, "question": "It's a God-fearing bad boy sees the light, parallels?", "qSentId": 195}, {"answer": "I think sometimes you read a script and you don't know why, you just think I connect with this, you know.", "docId": "111009pmt", "aSentId": 198, "question": "As you were filming, were you thinking -- I mean very different story line, but you know?", "qSentId": 197}, {"answer": "Absolutely.", "docId": "111009pmt", "aSentId": 204, "question": "It's a cliche question, but did it make you reassess yourself, your sense of what's important in life?", "qSentId": 203}, {"answer": "I'm -- I was brought up a Catholic.", "docId": "111009pmt", "aSentId": 214, "question": "Are you very religious?", "qSentId": 213}, {"answer": "I'm away.", "docId": "111009pmt", "aSentId": 229, "question": "Where are you?", "qSentId": 228}, {"answer": "Yes.", "docId": "111009pmt", "aSentId": 234, "question": "Sam?", "qSentId": 233}, {"answer": "Yes, I can hear you.", "docId": "111009pmt", "aSentId": 236, "question": "Can you hear me?", "qSentId": 235}, {"answer": "It hangs with you for awhile, and with this movie, there was very much a cumulative effect, because you know from day one you find yourself playing more and more of these scenes where you're either having some kind of breakdown via your drugs or family pressures.", "docId": "111009pmt", "aSentId": 240, "question": "When you finish scenes like that, how do you unwind after, can you or does it hang with you for a long time?", "qSentId": 239}, {"answer": "Yes, I do.", "docId": "111009pmt", "aSentId": 246, "question": "ORGAN: -- by what you had to see?", "qSentId": 245}, {"answer": "Yes.", "docId": "111009pmt", "aSentId": 256, "question": "Have you asked yourself that question?", "qSentId": 255}, {"answer": "I mean, I would give anybody free power to do whatever they wanted to if it was a family member of mine, and I myself would do it.", "docId": "111009pmt", "aSentId": 258, "question": "What would be the answer?", "qSentId": 257}, {"answer": "I don't know if I ever worked that out.", "docId": "111009pmt", "aSentId": 280, "question": "So, when did you realize this kind of look that you have was going to turn women wild?", "qSentId": 279}, {"answer": "I don't know.", "docId": "111009pmt", "aSentId": 305, "question": "I mean, these all just a brand extension, isn't it, all these kinds of stuff?", "qSentId": 304}, {"answer": "Yes.", "docId": "111009pmt", "aSentId": 322, "question": "But is there -- is there a turning point for that when people start to say what's up with you, then?", "qSentId": 321}, {"answer": "Yes.", "docId": "111009pmt", "aSentId": 334, "question": "Does your mother want to see her little boy settle down?", "qSentId": 333}, {"answer": "I don't think she wants little Gerards.", "docId": "111009pmt", "aSentId": 336, "question": "Get married, have little Gerards running around?", "qSentId": 335}, {"answer": "I mean, I could give you something, and then walk out of here and see a woman that's absolute opposite and go -- oh, wow, because I don't think there's a definite type.", "docId": "111009pmt", "aSentId": 343, "question": "Have you worked out what your dream woman would be, from all the experience you've had playing the field, have you actually worked out in your head what kind of characteristics and looks the one needs to have?", "qSentId": 342}, {"answer": "I love vivacious, but I love a good heart.", "docId": "111009pmt", "aSentId": 349, "question": "What kind of personality?", "qSentId": 348}, {"answer": "And fun.", "docId": "111009pmt", "aSentId": 352, "question": "Good humor attract for you?", "qSentId": 351}, {"answer": "Oh, God, I'm looking over.", "docId": "111009pmt", "aSentId": 364, "question": "If you could choose one partner for a desert island, if I was going to send you there for a year, who would it be?", "qSentId": 363}, {"answer": "You know, once I talked to Michael -- we used to discuss big issues, including life and death.", "docId": "111009pmt", "aSentId": 394, "question": "What did you mean by that?", "qSentId": 393}, {"answer": "Fame in itself is an addictive drug.", "docId": "111009pmt", "aSentId": 404, "question": "Is fame in itself an addictive drug?", "qSentId": 403}, {"answer": "Well, Michael only called me when he was totally sober and was off drugs.", "docId": "111009pmt", "aSentId": 410, "question": "What did you know about his drug consumption?", "qSentId": 409}, {"answer": "It's a common story, Piers.", "docId": "111009pmt", "aSentId": 434, "question": "What's your understanding about the repercussions of what we're watching here on screen?", "qSentId": 433}, {"answer": "Well, in a sense, we're all multiple personalities.", "docId": "111009pmt", "aSentId": 454, "question": "Or was it a bit of an act?", "qSentId": 453}, {"answer": "HOPRA: Well, Piers, I wasn't there at those rehearsals.", "docId": "111009pmt", "aSentId": 484, "question": "What was your understanding of his physical condition through this period?", "qSentId": 483}, {"answer": "I don't think so, and neither a cardiologist or an endocrinologist should administer.", "docId": "111009pmt", "aSentId": 511, "question": "Are either of you legally allowed to administer Propofol in a private house?", "qSentId": 510}, {"answer": "There were a couple of interventions to no avail.", "docId": "111009pmt", "aSentId": 527, "question": "Why did no one perform a kind of intervention and just try and get him off this stuff?", "qSentId": 526}, {"answer": "Yes, that's the basic idea.", "docId": "111009pmt", "aSentId": 548, "question": "Is that the tenet of this book?", "qSentId": 547}, {"answer": "LODINOW: Oh, yes, many scientists believe in God.", "docId": "111009pmt", "aSentId": 562, "question": "Any of the top ones?", "qSentId": 561}, {"answer": "Well, first of all, I don't say that I don't believe in god.", "docId": "111009pmt", "aSentId": 567, "question": "Isn't there a contradiction there?", "qSentId": 566}, {"answer": "I don't think people are that interested -- I don't think people are really that interested in my personal views.", "docId": "111009pmt", "aSentId": 570, "question": "Do you?", "qSentId": 569}, {"answer": "I believe in a kind of God.", "docId": "111009pmt", "aSentId": 583, "question": "Do you believe in God?", "qSentId": 582}, {"answer": "Let me go to Deepak.", "docId": "111009pmt", "aSentId": 590, "question": "And so, you know, if you want to go in that direction, you should ask, like Deepak does, where do those laws come from?", "qSentId": 589}, {"answer": "HOPRA: Well, it's the eternal mystery.", "docId": "111009pmt", "aSentId": 601, "question": "What do you think?", "qSentId": 600}, {"answer": "We could be here all day with this.", "docId": "111009pmt", "aSentId": 614, "question": "What happens to me after I die?", "qSentId": 613}, {"answer": "I think when, you know, ashes to ashes, dust to dust.", "docId": "111009pmt", "aSentId": 619, "question": "Where do you think you go when you die, Leonard?", "qSentId": 618}, {"answer": "You know, I would love to think that it's not.", "docId": "111009pmt", "aSentId": 623, "question": "That's the end of Leonard?", "qSentId": 622}, {"answer": "I think we go back to the infinite consciousness where we emerged from.", "docId": "111009pmt", "aSentId": 632, "question": "Deepak?", "qSentId": 631}]